{"data":[{"question":"A country can't be prosperously if it's not quite independent.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"A","b":"prosperously","c":"quite","d":"independent","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prosperously-> prosperous","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"They went on smoking all through during the meal.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"went on","b":"smoking","c":"during","d":"meal","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- During->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"These new machine have put an end to queuing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"These","b":"machine","c":"an","d":"to","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Machine-> machines","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The instructions say you just add boiling waters to the soup powder.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"instructions","b":"just","c":"boiling","d":"waters","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Waters-> waters","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The house seemed to have been unoccupying for several months.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"seemed","b":"been","c":"unoccupying","d":"for","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Unoccupying-> unoccupied","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"You must drive more slowly than in town.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"must","b":"more","c":"slowly","d":"than","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Than->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Be sure to say goodbye to your grandmother before you will leave.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to say","b":"to","c":"before","d":"will leave","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Will leave-> leave","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"The rate of inflation has fallen steadily during recently months.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"inflation","b":"fallen","c":"steadily","d":"recently","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Recently-> recent","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Most people consider that stealing was wrong.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Most","b":"that","c":"stealing","d":"was","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Was-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"},{"question":"Dickens's last novel was unfinished when he had died.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Dickens's","b":"last","c":"unfinished","d":"had died","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- Had died-> died","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"13","type":"1"}]}